[birds chirping]
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[Ruche whimpering]
[gasps]
-There it is.
-[gasps]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Angel's Playbox Entrance.
Recommended level, 50.
[whooshing]
[cape rustling]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[both gasp]
[PATCHWORK BEAR 1]
Bear! Bear! Bear!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[Patchwork Bear 1 roaring]
-[Elymas grunting]
-[sword slashing]
[grunts, yells]
[Patchwork Bear 1 groans]
[PATCHWORK BEAR 2] Bear!
Okay, same plan as before.
Let's go.
[grunts] Right!
[Elymas grunts]
-[Patchwork Bear 2 groans]
-[yells]
[Patchwork Bear 2 groans]
[sword slashes]
[Ruche squeals delightedly]
[giggles]
How was that?
Am I being useful, Mr. Elymas?
Yeah. Thank you.
I feel really grateful
you decided to team up with me.
[squeals excitedly]
[giggling]
Guess you wanted
to get your hands
on these little Bear Shields
pretty badly, didn't you?
Should we collect
10 more of them?
[ELYMAS] No.
You've gained enough levels.
The real work starts right now.
Mm. Huh?
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level 20 has been reached.
[RUCHE] Oh, wow! You're right!
When did that happen?
-[giggles]
-[ELYMAS] At this point,
the new goal for us...
is hunting Golden Raana.
[gasps]
Uh. Golden Raana?!
[croaks]
[♪ opening theme song playing]
BEGIN ADVENTURE
EPISODE 7
GOLDEN RAANA FARMING
[Ruche gasps]
[whimpers]
[ELYMAS] Raana.
They're the frog monsters
I defeated
after coming to this place.
And when I played Magic World,
they were quite
a beloved trash mob.
Rampart Reflection! [grunts]
[electrical crackling]
Although there are
many variations out here,
our current target
is both the rarest
and most coveted,
known as the Golden Raana.
Given the situation
we're in now,
I determined our best move
would be to farm
this dungeon next.
The Golden Raana has
a really low spawn rate,
but what makes them
so sought after
is the high chance
that they'll drop
an unbelievably valuable item.
[Golden Raana croaks]
Furthermore, their Attack
and Magic are extremely low
despite having such high levels,
and they lack
any offensive skills.
-Ah?
-In short,
these things are weak in combat,
offer tons of XP,
and provide
truly valuable drops.
So you couldn't ask
for a juicier monster!
Oh!
[ELYMAS] Luckily,
there are a good number
of bonus characters
like the Golden Raana.
Or, as they're
affectionately known
in Magic World, Golden Toads.
And a large number
of players would tell you
that farming them
was their favorite part
of the entire game.
They frequently spawn
in the middle of levels
in the Angel's Playbox,
so this is where
we need to search.
We have an advantage
when it comes to hunting
the different monsters
that appear in this dungeon.
I know where each one
is likely to be.
-[Ruche grunts]
-[gasps]
Hey, um, I've heard things
about the Golden Raana too.
They say a person
can live off of just one
of those things for years.
Well, at least
that's what the adventurers
at the bar told me.
Really? That makes things
even simpler, then.
[RUCHE] But they also mentioned
something else.
Apparently,
they can move so fast
that they're almost
impossible to catch.
And even if you land a hit,
they still
don't take any damage.
-[croaks]
-[RUCHE] It's not unusual
for people to chase them farther
than they expected,
and then
they find themselves surrounded
by a whole bunch of monsters.
[whimpers] It's been said
that adventurers have died
because of those
awful little creatures!
So they're a lot more dangerous
than you might think they are!
[whimpering]
[ELYMAS] Mm. That's right.
This world and the game
are two different things.
Out here, death is the end.
People naturally tend
to choose safe,
dependable builds
for their survival.
-[monsters growling]
-[adventurer whimpers]
Farming Golden Raana
must be more difficult
than I thought.
After all,
those things are imbued
with extraordinary
Speed and Defense.
[croaks]
They're also totally immune
to elemental attacks,
status effects,
and debuffs of any kind.
Ah! If we went up
against a monster like that,
don't you think
we'd be powerless?!
I mean, sure,
the Ironpiercer knife
you gave me is really effective
going up against
high-Defense targets.
But I seriously have my doubts
it would do any damage
to a Golden Raana.
That said, I don't think I could
even catch up to one anyway.
Hmm. Yeah, you're right.
We're talking about creatures
that possess
a Speed of 67
and Defense of 200.
And Ironpiercer's
15% Defense Penetration
would be completely ineffective
against them,
-unfortunately.
-[sighs]
So then--
[ELYMAS] As a Pierrot,
Ruche is swift
and light on her feet.
But its Speed is still
more than double hers.
As a slow Heavy Knight,
on the other hand,
it can reach speeds
that are more than triple mine.
Also, its Defense is 200.
Which means that
even if I were to execute
a perfect Rampart Reflection,
it would be rendered
ineffective.
Like Ironpiercer,
Vital Slice has
15% Defense Penetration.
So it's not enough
to deal any real damage.
-[RUCHE] Are, uh--
-Hmm?
Are we sure
this isn't impossible now?
-Don't worry.
-[gasps]
Because I've got a plan.
[gasps]
Even its seemingly
perfect defense has holes,
so we'll use them
to our advantage.
Huh?!
But-- But do you have any skills
that can really damage
something as durable
as a Golden Raana?
Because honestly,
I've never heard
of Heavy Knights
having anything like that.
[chuckles]
Uh?
'Kay, Ruche, you've got this.
[gasps] Hang on!
You're counting on me?!
Anyway, after all
the leveling you've done
while grinding
through the monsters here,
you should have
eight skill points.
[gasps]
[ELYMAS] Right now,
you need to put all of them
into the Fool's Acrobatics.
The two skills you'll need
are going to be essential
to making our strategy work.
Uh, I'm glad to know
you've got high hopes for me
and actually believe
I'll be able to pull this off.
But I just don't have
that kind of power.
-[♪ dramatic music playing]
-[gasps]
-[monster grunting]
-[Elymas grunts]
-[monster growls]
-[sword slashes]
-[monster groaning]
[Ruche gasps]
[gasps]
[ELYMAS] Okay, Ruche.
Let's run while we can.
[RUCHE] Okay. I think
I could finish it off,
but you're sure, right?
Yeah. That isn't the target
we're after,
and the minute
it feels like it's cornered,
it'll start summoning
its allies here.
[gasps] Are you sure
we really want to narrow
our focus to Golden Raana
and run past any other monsters
we cross paths with?
With all your civility
and knowledge,
if we could defeat
the other ones we find
while making our way
through this place,
I could probably gain
three more levels
before we even reach
the end of the day.
It's fine. At our current level,
farming Golden Raana
is the perfect way
to make progress quickly.
[panting] Huh?
Good. That thing
isn't coming after us.
[Ruche grunts]
[sighs heavily]
Well, I assumed we wouldn't find
what we're looking for
right away.
Are you serious?
Yes. Even if we were
to search all day,
we might come across
two of them.
[Ruche gasps] Wait.
You mean those little creatures
are really that rare?
-Indeed.
-[gasps]
But Golden Raana
are worth every bit
of our time and effort.
[whimpers, gulps]
That said, no matter how high
your Luck stat may be,
they're still a pretty
difficult monster to encounter.
Just let me know if you begin
to feel anxious or unhappy,
okay?
[Ruche grunts]
-Don't you worry!
-Hmm?
I was only a little anxious,
that's all.
I'll follow you wherever you go,
Mr. Elymas.
I appreciate it,
but there's no reason
for you to hold back.
Let's go farm 100
or even 1,000 Golden Raana!
I'm ready
to show you I can do it!
[laughs awkwardly]
[ELYMAS] I'm glad
to hear she's feeling motivated,
but Rondalm's market
would be thrown into total chaos
if we managed to farm that many.
Huh?
[croaks]
Um, isn't that...
[gasps]
[Raana croaking]
[both gasp]
[ELYMAS] A Golden Raana!
[croaks]
[Ruche grunts]
-Don't you worry!
-Hmm?
I'll follow you
wherever you go, Mr. Elymas.
Huh?
[croaks]
Um, isn't that...
[both gasp]
[croaking]
[ELYMAS] A Golden Raana!
[croaks]
[grunts, gasps]
We found one a lot sooner
than I was expecting.
[Ruche gasps]
We finally saw one.
What are we supposed to do now?
Just take deep breaths, Ruche.
-[gasps]
-To defeat this thing,
we need to remain calm
and collected.
[Ruche gasps] Got it.
[breathing deeply]
EXHALE
INHALE
-[croaks]
-[Ruche gasps]
Were you able
to raise Fool's Acrobatics to 10
using your skill points
from leveling up earlier?
[gasps] Yes!
And I acquired
the two skills you mentioned.
Do you really think
they'll help us out?
Yes. Now let's go through
with the plan.
Mm. Okay!
[ELYMAS] I'll stand right here
and wait for the Golden Raana.
Get on the other side
and start herding it towards me.
[whimpering]
[ELYMAS] Ruche?
You've so got this, Ruche.
I can do it,
I can do it, I can do it,
I can do it, I--
I can do it, I can do it.
I can do it. I can do it.
[ELYMAS] Hey there, no pressure.
It's all right if you mess up.
[RUCHE] Tense, tense, tense...
Just take a few
big breaths, okay?
[Ruche gasps]
[taking deep breaths]
♪
I'm good to go, sir.
Now let's get this Raana!
[ELYMAS] Golden Raana
begin fleeing
when they sense an adventurer
within a four-meter proximity.
Coincidentally,
the corridors
in the Angel's Playbox
are four meters wide.
[croaks]
Even if a Golden Raana
is hugging the edges,
there's not enough distance
to sneak by undetected.
-[Ruche panting]
-However,
that's only
if you're walking on the floor.
[Ruche panting]
[RUCHE] Acrobatic Amble!
[panting]
[grunts]
[croaks]
[croaking]
There's no escape!
Doppellusion!
DOPPELLUSION
[gasps] These narrow corridors
make slipping past
those illusions impossible.
And Golden Raana
are far too cowardly
to charge into them.
It's a sitting duck.
They can't be blinded,
thanks to their immunity
to status effects.
Hallucinate doesn't work
for the same reason.
Thankfully,
they can still be fooled
by the illusions
created by Doppellusion.
It's a weak spot
in their resistances
that we can take advantage of.
[gasps]
Watch out!
It's running your direction!
[croaking]
[ELYMAS] What also works well
is Shadow Stomp!
[grunts]
[ELYMAS] It all comes down
to whether or not I can land it.
The narrow corridors help,
but it's still three times
faster than me.
Plus my shadow's
only 50 centimeters long.
[sighs] Enough of that.
[croaking]
This was my idea
in the first place,
and I'm not going to fail!
I bought these Magic Stones
when we got Ironpiercer.
Their healing effects
are too weak
to make them worth using.
[croaking]
But they can also do this!
[grunts]
[croaks]
[Elymas grunts]
Shadow Stomp!
[struggling]
[croaks]
Golden Raana, we've got you now!
Mr. Elymas, we trapped it!
[giggles]
That loot and XP
is as good as ours!
[croaking]
[Ruche giggles]
Wait. It may be stuck,
but how are you
supposed to actually kill it?
[croaking]
FLAIL
We can only hurt it
by landing critical hits on it.
[RUCHE] Critical hits?!
-[knight grunts]
-[ELYMAS] Yes.
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Critical.
[ELYMAS] When you're able
to successfully read
your opponent's movements
and land what would
be considered the perfect hit,
you deal 1.5 times the damage
and ignore half
your target's defense.
I get it now!
And since
the Golden Raana's trapped,
you can try for
as many critical hits
as you need, right?
[chuckles] I believe in you.
Best of luck!
Well,
my critical hits won't deal
enough damage to affect it,
so someone else
needs to finish it off.
Oh. Huh?
It's like I said,
I'm counting on you, Ruche.
What?!
[ELYMAS] Landing critical hits
requires both skill and luck.
-[knight grunts]
-[AUTOMATED VOICE] Critical.
[ELYMAS] And obviously,
I'm in no position
to go for critical hits
right now, since I can't move.
But-- But-- But I barely
ever scored any critical hits!
How am I supposed
to get them now?
It'd be impossible
with normal attacks,
but don't forget
about the original skill
that you already had
when we got here.
Remember Dice Thrust?
[gasps] Wait. You want me
to use Dice Thrust?
Ruche. Listen.
You may be risking your life
out there,
but you still don't have
any decent attack skills.
You just stand around
and soak up hits.
Truth is,
you aren't useful to us.
You managed to finally learn
an attack skill, huh?
[gasps]
But it's less useful
than a normal attack.
Can't say I'm surprised one bit.
[sighs]
That skill...
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Skill,
Dice Thrust. A thrusting skill.
Rolls a six-sided die
and grants a bonus effect
based on the rolled result.
Hmm?
Yeah. I guess that could work!
See? A six gets you...
[BOTH] A guaranteed critical!
[ELYMAS] Rolling a six
multiplies your attack
by 1.3,
and also guarantees
a critical hit.
That's a total of 1.95 times
the base damage.
On top of that,
Ironpiercer's 15% Penetration
and a Critical's
50% Penetration stack.
So a six ultimately hits
with 1.95 times attack
and 65% Defense Penetration.
[gasps]
-[croaking]
-[RUCHE] Still,
do you really think
this can work?
Some classes
may be late bloomers,
and some skills may have
limited use cases.
But no class
or skill is useless.
Don't let
the short-sighted assessments
of others bother you.
And as far as
Cline's party goes,
you only seemed
underwhelming to them.
I'll say it again, Ruche.
I need you in my party. Got it?
[gasps]
I hope you'll keep
lending me your strength.
[grunts]
[RUCHE] I'll do it.
If someone has
that much faith in me,
I won't let them down! [panting]
Otherwise, what's the point
in being an adventurer?
Yeah! All right! Let's go!
[panting]
Dice Thrust!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[squeals excitedly]
[gasps, chuckles]
[croaks]
[AUTOMATED VOICE] Critical.
[Ruche grunts]
[grunts]
-[Golden Raana groans]
-[thuds]
[clinking]
[Ruche gasps]
Whoa. We actually did it!
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level 27 has been reached.
There's no way!
I made it
all the way to level 27!
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Level 30 has been reached.
It's nice that Golden Raana
are worth a lot of EXP.
But the best part
is the valuable items
they can drop.
The drop rate is right at 50%.
[gasps]
[squeals excitedly]
[chuckles excitedly]
[AUTOMATED VOICE]
Dazzling Raana Decorative Blade.
Attack, plus 12.
Market price, 17 million gold.
A glittering Raana short sword.
A hunk
of high-purity Raana Gold.
[squeals excitedly]
Whoa. A Dazzling Raana
Decorative Blade!
[♪ closing theme song playing]
[ELYMAS] Both Ruche and I
gained tons of levels
by killing the Golden Raana.
But it's still not enough.
That loot drop
was only worth a fraction
of what it will cost
to buy that skillbook.
Grinding levels
and stockpiling gold
is a lot of fun.
However,
this world isn't a game.
Next time, "Wandering."
Falling in this world
means dying for real.
Being gone forever.